偷Han的盘子
Stealing Han's dishes,
这样我们就不用洗在家的盘子 简直是天才
so we don't have to clean our at home is genius.
也有点可悲
And a little sad.
开什么玩笑 自我今早大姨妈光顾之后
You kidding? This is the greatest thing that's happened to me
对我来说 这简直是最棒的事了
since I got my period this morning.
Max Caroline 你们在偷我的盘子
Max, Caroline, you're stealing my dishes?
见鬼 我没想到这个高度你也可以看见
Damn it, I didn't think you could see up this high.
我也没想到你会这么堕落
And I didn't think you could sink this low.
好吧 快停下 你们用
Okay, stop, you're already robbing me blind
"我只是一个服务生"这种小把戏顺了很多东西
with your "I'm a waitress" Scam.
抱歉 但是家里现在实在是一团糟
Sorry, but things have gotten kind of messy at home.
昨天 我不得不洗个澡
Yesterday, I had to take
就为了洗干净我拿着的喷淋头
a shower to shower off the shower I took.
你们两个应该雇一个清洁女工
You two should get a cleaning lady.
我就雇了一个女工来收拾我的公寓
I have a woman I pay to clean my apartment.
价钱蛮贵 但是如果你不和她做爱的话
She is expensive, but she may charge you less
她可能少收你点
if you don't also have sex on her.
我去问问看吧
I'll look into it.
我的祖母会免费收拾屋子
My grandmother cleaned the house free of charge.
当然 在这件事上 她也没什么发言权了
Of course she didn't have a say in the matter.
我们还是问问Sophie吧 她有清洁服务的公司
Let's just ask Sophie. She has a cleaning service.
我们必须做点什么
We have to do something.
昨天 我看见一只小强从我们公寓跑出来
Yesterday, I saw a roach walk out of our apartment.
听着
Look.
我要把我对那个想用
I'm gonna tell you what I told that guy
我翘臀偷运鸦片的人说的话答你
who asked me to use my butt to smuggle opium.
我会做的
I'll do it!
== 破产姐妹 第三季 第9集 ==
【H-SGDK】字幕组倾情奉献
== 翻译:嘿嘿 顾顾 蛋蛋 特特 ==
== 校对&时间轴:天之行者  统筹&后期:尧之雪 ==
本字幕仅用于交流 学习之用
禁止用于任何商业用途 否则后果自负
快点起来 Max
Be ready, Max.
我们要在清洁女工来之前离开这儿
We have to leave as soon as the cleaning lady gets here.
这是她们的潜规矩
It's housekeeper etiquette.
以前 这种时候 我会去上单车班 然后和朋友们吃午餐
In my old life, I go to spin class and lunch with friends,
但是现在我们就只是一起出去
but you and I will just go outside
看看那个刚从监狱出来的家伙
and watch the guy who just
在电线杠子上做做引体向上
got out of jail do pull-ups on the light post.
Calvin出狱了
Calvin's out?
我才不走
I'm not gonna leave.
我要看着她把这些脏东西收拾干净
I want to watch her clean up my mess.
没错 小宝贝
Yeah, baby.
我等了一辈子就是为了个仆人
I've waited my whole life to have a servant.
在你刚来的前几周我还幻想着你会是个好仆人
I thought you were gonna be it for the first few weeks
然后我意识到 你什么都不会做
and then I realized you can't do anything.
尽管Sophie给我们折扣了
And even though Sophie gave us a discount,
这个小仆人还是要叫我 女王陛下
the maid still has to call me "Your Highness."
那是因为 我现在已经自嗨起来了
Mostly because I'm pretty "Highness" Right now.
嗨 菇凉们
Hi, girls.
我来了
Here I am.
来自"苏菲的选择清洁服务公司"的Sophie
Sophie from Sophie's Choice Cleaning Service.
认识一下你们的清洁女工吧 Paulina
Meet your cleaning lady Paulina.
Paulina 见见菇凉们
Paulina, meet the girls.
嗯
Mm.
她也很想握手 不过她只有一只胳膊
She'd shake hands, but she only has one arm.
Sophie 她能听见你说什么
Sophie, she can hear you.
那又怎样 我知道我只有一只胳膊
So what? I know I'm missing arm.
这也不是什么新鲜事
It's not news.
她丢了一只胳膊
So she lost an arm.
我在楼下垃圾处理场丢了一只金耳环
I lost my gold earring down the garbage disposal
但是我实在是不想下去再找了
but I was too afraid to reach into it
因为 嗯 嗯哼(我可不想也没只胳膊)
because, well, yeah.
不用担心
Don't worry.
虽然我只有一只胳膊 但我的表现好像我有三只一样
I have one arm but I clean like I have three.
我要再补点妆 然后就可以开始了
I put on more makeup, then I start.
不好意思 在叫清洁女工的时候
I'm sorry. I didn't realize when I ordered a cleaning lady
我没意识要说找有两只胳膊的
I had to specify I wanted one with two arms.
你可负担不起两只胳膊
You can't afford two arms.
你说你想要价格优惠点
You said you wanted a good price.
一只胳膊 一半的价格
Half the arms, half the price.
她就是这样丢了她的胳膊的吗 Sophie
Is that how she lost the arm, Sophie?
你把它砍断了 这样就可以给我们个折扣
You cut it off so we could get a discount?
哦 是的 没错
Oh, yeah, sure. Yeah, I
我把她的胳膊锯掉了 这样可以给你们便宜10元钱
sawed off her arm so I could save you 10 bucks.
我先从卧室开始了
I start in bedroom.
等一下 在你开始前 有一个问题
Wait, before you do, one question.
你的胳膊是怎么没了的 和James Franco一样的情况吗
How'd you lose it? James Franco situation?
为了脱困 你必须断掉一只胳膊
You had to cut it off to get loose?
你没有否认
You're not saying no.
好了 不要再谈这个话题了
Oh, you know what, let's not go there.
它发生了 都过去了
You know, it happened, it was in the past.
我被困在了一个大卡车下面
I was trapped under this big truck.
我们都懂了
We get it.
我开车把你胳膊压断了
I drove over your arm.
不要花心思在里面找我上好的珠宝了
Hey, don't even bother looking for my good jewelry in there
因为它们都在这里
because I'm already wearing all of it.
哦 我太嫉妒了 因为我没有胳膊 去戴那些廉价的首饰
Oh, I'm jealous I don't have arm to wear cheap jewelry.
Max 我觉得她好可怜 看见了吗 这就是为什么你应该离开的原因
Max, I feel bad for her. See? This is why you leave.
以防她们画着浓妆出现 也没有两只胳膊
In case they show up with too much makeup and not enough arms.
放松 她很坚强 让我想起了年轻时的我
Relax, she's tough. Reminds me of a young me.
我最好赶紧把我的小药片藏起来
Which means I better go hide my pills from her.
Max 她让我害怕
Max, she scares me.
得了 她没有胳膊
Oh, come on, she's armless.
事情进展的顺利吗 需要我帮助吗
Everything okay? You need any help?
我能工作到现在 可没靠着帮助
I didn't get this far in this business by taking help.
快帮帮我 你没看见我只有一只胳膊吗
Help me! Can't you see I got one arm?
没关系
Not gonna be a problem.
我有时会帮助我的女佣
I would occasionally help my maid...
- 你对这个不敢兴趣  - 用力抬起来
- You're not interested. - Lift!
用力 没用的小姑凉 抬起来
Lift, weak girl. Lift.
Max 过来 帮我们把你的床垫抬起来
Max, come here. We need help lifting your mattress.
能过来帮个忙吗
Can you give us a hand?
不 给我放下 放下 别把床垫掀起来
No! Leave it alone! Leave it alone! Don't lift up the mattress!
哟 黄书啊
Ah, porno.
你思想跟这公寓一样的脏
Your mind is as dirty as your apartment!
对 就是黄书 怎么了 有什么大不了的
Yes, it's porn. So what? What's the big deal?
不就是赤身裸体
It's just the body in its natural form,
在摩托车上搔首弄姿嘛
spread-eagle on a motorcycle.
这些人怎么有一种复古风
Why is so much of it from the '80s?
我就喜欢大胡子
I like mustaches, okay?
我顺便还拿它来找我爸
And it's multitasking. I'm looking for my father.
别看了 别看了
Stop looking. Stop looking right now.
怎么这么羞射 Porn hub可是你的电脑首页
Why are you suddenly embarrassed? Porn hub is your homepage.
喔 这是个糕点学校的手册
Hey, is this a brochure for pastry school?
你为什么把它藏着
Why are you hiding a pastry school brochure?
你看着才像个糕点学校的手册
Your face is a pastry school brochure!
Max 你对去学做糕点感兴趣真是太好了
Max, it's great you're interested in pastry school.
我不明白你为什么会尴尬
I don't know why you're embarrassed.
你这张脸才叫人尴尬
- Your face is embarrassed!
别这样 我真觉得我们可以一起讨论讨论
Come on, I really think that this is something we should talk about.
我们最需要讨论的是你这张脸
Your face is something we should talk about!
你把那吓人女弄疯了
You made the scary one mad.
真够蠢的
That was dumb move.
你这张脸才叫蠢
Your face was a dumb move!
Max
Max?
Max 你离家出走后没回来过
Max, you never came home after you stormed out,
所以我把你的制服给带来了
so I brought you your uniform.
Max 你在嘛
Max?
我现在住这儿
I live here now.
这是我的新室友们 扫帚和拖把
My new roommates, the broom and the mop,
他们可不会鬼鬼祟祟地偷看我的东西
don't sneak around looking at my stuff.
这里什么都有
I got everything I need.
威士忌 牙刷还有牙膏
Whiskey, toothbrush, toothpaste.
好吧 也许你的扫把舍友
Well, maybe your new broommate
会在你喝醉的时候让你停下来
will hold back your hair when you drink too much.
看你这样子 也就会在这小时内喝醉
Which, from the looks of it, will be in about an hour.
Max 我们真要好好谈谈这小册子了
Max, we really need to talk about this brochure.
听着 只是因为我有了这个小册子
Look, just because I have a pastry school brochure
并不意味着我真的要去那个学校
doesn't mean I'm actually gonna go to pastry school.
就像虽然我有那些黄色杂志
Just like having those porn magazines
但我也不会真的去骑在老虎身上
doesn't mean I'm actually gonna ride around on a tiger
和水手一起干些黄暴动作 当然这也说不准
performing unspeakable acts with sailors, probably.
糕点学校就跟黄书一样
Pastry school is the same as porn.
只是个愚蠢的幻想罢了
It's just a dumb fantasy.
当然不是这样
Pastry school is not like porn.
这小册子里边可没有介绍"羊角拉拉爱爱包"
There is nothing in this brochure about a girl-on-girl croissant.
这牙膏真好喝
That's good toothpaste.
别用酒刷你的牙了 我们待会儿还得上班
Please stop brushing your teeth. We have a shift to do later.
好 我们来谈谈曼哈顿糕点学校
Okay, the Manhattan school of pastry...
你这张脸就是曼哈顿糕点学校
Your face is the Manhattan school of pastry.
它不是 你清楚得很
You know it isn't.
Max 你可以去看看的
Max, you could go here for real.
一年学费只有3000 虽然有些多 但还可行
Tuition is only $3,000 a year. A lot, but doable.
很多 但可行的
"A lot but doable?"
我们是在谈糕点学校 还是在说打烊前胖吃货男
Are we talking about pastry school or fat guy at last call?
我们来了 Max 你的梦想要开始了
Here we are, Max. Your dream starts now.
要到我能成为黑美人鱼生活的地方了
What, the one where I'm a black mermaid?
放松点 我们只是到处转转然后去领个申请表
Would you relax? We're just gonna look around and get an application.
看到这些超棒的设备了吗 如果你在这里学习 这些你都可以用
See all that gorgeous equipment you get to use if you went here?
终于你能有个搅拌钵 而不是一直用个挖空了的西瓜
Finally you'd have a mixing bowl that's not a hollowed-out watermelon.
救救我 她正在逼迫我
Can you help me? She's holding me against my will.
只是开个玩笑
She's kidding.
你再这么做 小姐
If you keep this up, young lady,
之后我不会给你买冰激凌的
you are not getting ice cream after.
好啦
Fine!
来吧 这是办公室
Come on, here's the office.
无所谓了 这事要完了吗
Whatever. Are we almost done here?
我上庭时候到了
I got a court date later.
- 你好 - 你好
- Hi. - Hi.
你好
Hi.
我不太清楚是不是来对了地方
I'm not sure we're in the right place.
有谁真清楚吗
Are any of us, really?
我们想要拿一张申请表 能帮帮我们嘛
We'd like an application. Could you help us?
喔 老天 真希望能
Oh, God, I hope so.
我没想到再回来工作的第一天就这么有压力
I wasn't expecting something this high-pressure my first day back.
告诉你们 我之前在精神病院待过
Let's just say I've been under observation at the nuthouse.
好了 申请表
Okay, application.
是为了Max 就是她 你们的小册子很吸引她
It's for Max, here. She was very impressed by your brochure.
喔 糕点学校 很令人激动 不是吗
Oh, pastry school. Exciting, right?
我以前是这里的大厨 然后就不是了
I was a chef here once. And then I wasn't.
喔 看 找到了申请表
Oh, look. Found the application.
噢 真没想到我能处理好
Wow. Really didn't think I was gonna be able to handle that.
Bebe 如果你
Bebe, if you...
喔 你好 早上好
Oh. Bonjour. Good morning.
Nicolas大厨 这两个女孩是来拿申请表的
Chef Nicolas, these girls are here for an application.
别担心 我都弄好了 差点没成 但是我还是做到了
Don't worry, I handled it. Almost didn't, then I did.
干得好 Bebe
Nice work, Bebe.
喔 我听出来了法国腔哦 还真是的
Oh, do I detect a French accent? Oui?
我的老天 简直不忍直视
Oh, my God, I can't watch.
确实是法国人 我是Nicolas Saintcroix
French, indeed. I'm chef Nicolas Saintcroix,
这里的老板兼首席大厨 欢迎光临
owner and head chef. Bienvenue.
我是Caroline Channing
Caroline Channing.
能走了吗
Is it over yet?
这是Max 申请表是给她的
This is Max. The application's for her.
嘿 法国佬 你也吃蜗牛
'Sup, Frenchie? You eat snails?
看起来Bebe忘了还有第二页
It looks like Bebe forgot the second page.
喔天哪 忘记有第二页了 这可不妙
Oh, boy, forgot the second page. That's not good.
我觉得我处理好了 可是我并没有
I thought I handled it. Didn't handle it.
没事儿的Bebe  吸气
It's okay, Bebe. Breathe in.
呼气
Breathe out.
真管用
That's good stuff.
她以前很棒
She was quite brilliant.
然后就傻了
Then she wasn't.
给 把它填了 接下来还有个糕点考试
Here. Fill that out. And the next step is the pastry exam.
申请者要做个传统的果馅饼
Applicants will have to make a classic tart,
明天带来让我试吃一下
bring them in tomorrow for me to taste,
然后就开始学习 怎么样
and we will go from there. Sound good?
随便啦 也许我会考虑一下
Whatever. Maybe I'll think about it.
好吧 也许吧 很高兴见到你们
Okay, well, maybe you will. Nice meeting you both.
大厨 希望明天见到你
Hope to see you tomorrow, chef.
他叫我大厨
He called me chef!
- 耶 我们去吃冰激凌  - 不
- Yay! Let's go get ice cream! - No!
你该开始做果馅饼 明天就要交了
You should get started on that tart. It's due tomorrow.
我时间多得是 而且有压力才弄得好
I got plenty of time. Besides, pressure ups my game.
当有把枪顶在我脑门上的时候 我最有表现
I perform my best when there's a gun to my head.
随便找个前男友问问都行
Ask any of my ex-boyfriends.
我绝不这么准备考试
This is so not how I prepare for tests.
我以前为了子宫颈抹片检查都温习了三个星期
I studied three weeks for a pap smear.
别担心 我有把握
Don't worry, I got this.
果馅饼就是把布丁倒到饼干上 对吧
A tart's just like a cookie with some pudding on it, right?
Max 这儿怎么了
Max, what is going on in here?
原来果馅饼不仅仅是把布丁放在饼干上这么简单
Turns out a tart's more than a cookie with some pudding on it!
你已经在厨房呆了六个小时了 你说过你有把握
You've been in here six hours. You said you had this.
我本也是这么想的 结果并不是这样
I thought I had this! Turns out I don't!
我连个饼底都没弄好
I haven't even finished a shell.
我都不知道竟然还有个饼底 你知道吗
I didn't know there was a shell. Did you know there was a shell?
是人都知道有饼底
Everybody knows there's a shell!
你又抽什么风
What the shell is wrong with you?
我是个不会做果馅饼的贱女
I'm a tart who can't make a tart!
你用的时间都可以做九个饼底了
You could've made nine shells by now.
我做了 看 都在这里
I did. They're all in here. Look.
就像个饼底末日
It's like Shell-mageddon!
喔 去他的 这面团反正一会儿也得进垃圾桶
Oh, screw it. This one's gonna be there in a minute.
还是直接扔了吧
Let's just get it over with.
不 你能做到的 这里这里 这个看起来就很不错
No, you can do this. Here. Here. This still looks ready to go.
看我 看我 我真是浪费我这两条胳膊
Look at me. Look at me. I'm a waste of two arms.
我做不出来果馅饼
I can't make a tart!
果馅饼做的怎么样了
How's the tart coming?
Han 别没事儿找事儿 赶紧走
Han, you're not safe. Leave.
你连饼底都没弄好 这可是最简单的部份
You haven't even finished the shell? That's the easiest part!
Han 再废话这就是你那张脸的下场
Han, this is your face.
好吧 我该走了
Well, I should get going.
她的贱竟还能有突破
I didn't know she could take bitch to the next level.
我完了
I am so screwed!
终于遇到连甩胸也解决不了的问题了
I finally found a situation my boobs can't get me out of!了
Max 我对你有一百二十个信心
Hey, Max. Now, I have all the faith in the world in you.
但还是在超市买了个果馅饼给你
But here's a tart from Stop
以防你想交上这个代替
'n Shop in case you wanted to hand this one in.
不 Earl Max不是作弊的人
No, Earl. Max is not a cheater.
还有这种事
Since when?
她要自己做出来个果馅饼
She is going to make her own tart.
你出去吧
You, out.
我根本做不出来饼底
I am never gonna make this shell.
我连怎么放进烤盘里都不会
I can't even get it in the pan right.
Max 好像就是这么放
Max, that looks right.
饿滴神啊 我居然放进盘里了 我绝对能做出来
Oh, my God! I got it in the pan right! I can do this!
我就知道你能做到 我也帮上忙 咱们是闺蜜
You did it! I knew it! I helped you. We're besties.
你也欠揍的样 出去
You're not safe. Leave.
这么跟你说 Max
I'm telling you, Max,
我吃饼无数 你的绝对无敌
I've tasted a lot of tarts, and yours is delicious.
很多男人也都这么认为
You are not the first man to tell me that.
第一个这么说的 已经进监狱了
The first man to tell me that is in jail.
他来了 你看你看 他来了
Here he comes. Look at him. Here he comes.
下午好 女士们
Afternoon, ladies.
好个芝士锅啊 埃菲尔铁塔兄
Bien fondue, Eiffel Tower.
好吧
Okay.
感谢你们的到来 让我们开始品尝吧
Thank you for coming. Shall we begin the tasting?
很兴奋吧
This is exciting, huh?
把持住 少女
Keep it in your pants.
来尝果馅饼吧
And now for the tart.
这是Max的第一个
It's Max's first ever.
我吃了一小块
I ate a slice earlier and it was like
简直是天堂般美味
Having a little piece of heaven.
别这样 正常点
Don't do anything you're doing.
很薄 浓郁
It's flaky, creamy...
对于你的第一次尝试 相当不错
For a first attempt, I am very impressed.
不算啥 我只做了个果馅饼
Don't be. I made a tart.
又不是治好了疱疹
It's not like I cured herpes
也没发明能为汽水瞬间制冷的神奇微波炉
or invented a reverse microwave to instantly chill sodas.
好的 Max
Okay, Max.
我会和教员们讨论一下 然后告诉你结果
I will talk it over with my faculty and we will let you know.
我会给你个结果
I'll let you know.
搞定
Nailed that.
Max
Max!
别偷我的东西了 你已经有清洁工了
Stop stealing my things! You got a cleaning lady!
别紧张 我是来还东西的
Relax. I am returning what I took.
这些是你的盘子
Here's your plates.
还有你的提款卡 我从你钱包里顺的
Oh, and here's your ATM card. I lifted it from your wallet.
对了 还有你的钱包
Oh, and here's your wallet.
里面还应该有40块钱呀
There was $40 in here.
曾经有过
There sure was.
至少把我的丝芙兰购物卡也还回来吧
At least give me back my gift card from Sephora.
Caroline Han想把他的丝芙兰购物卡要回去
Caroline, Han wants his Sephora gift card back.
不可能了 我已经买了东西抹脸上了
Oh, that's not happening. It's already on my face.
Max 看 糕点学校的信
Max, look, it's from the pastry school.
哈哈 我的录取信
Whoo-hoo! My acceptance letter!
很多人在厕所里都提起我的JJ
Lot of people talking about my chili in that bathroom.
Oleg 过来 Han Earl 先别走
Oleg, come here. Han, Earl, stay.
你们要欠我个大大的人情了
You guys are about to owe me big.
我要让你们见证最不可能的奇迹了
I am gonna let you witness something extremely rare.
比大脚怪 UFO 或Han的小JJ还要稀有
More rare than a sighting of Bigfoot or a UFO or Han's penis.
你让我过来就是听这个
You held me here so I could hear that?
注意 最稀有的
Behold, the rarest sight of them all.
你们要见证天上真有馅饼掉到我头上了
You are about to see something good actually happen to me.
都听好
Listen to this.
亲爱的Black女士 经过对大批候选人的
"Dear Ms. Black, after careful consideration
慎重考虑 我们很遗憾地通知你
"Of our large pool of applicants, we regret to inform you..."
看来我没被录取
Oh, I guess I didn't get in.
话说回来 我们应该强烈要求她
Looking back, we probably should have insisted
自己先读一读的
she read that to herself, first.
我知道她为什么没被录取 因为她的名字
I know why she didn't get in. Her name.
他们一看Black这个姓 马上就否了
They saw the word "Black" And stopped reading.
这就是我没去成法学院的原因
That's why I didn't get into law school.
反正我也没申请
I also didn't apply.
太糟糕了 我去看看她怎么样了
This is terrible. I'm gonna go see if she's okay.
那个法国佬以为他是谁
Who does that French frog think he is?
他以为他尝过我的果馅饼
He thinks he can have the time of his life tasting my tart
就能抹嘴开溜吗
and then never see me again?
他居然不让我入学
He won't let me into his school?
我可不接受被拒
Well, I won't take no for an answer.
我现在就过去
I am going down there right now
拚个你死我活
and giving him a piece of my mind.
老娘冲出去了
I am storming out.
老娘又回来了
And I am storming back in.
天已经晚了 学校早关门了
It is dark outside. That school's not open.
你 嘲笑果馅饼的 我要和你谈谈
Hey, you. Tart tease, we need a word.
天啊
Oh, boy.
怎么 你喜欢我的糕点
What? You love my pastries
却要遗憾地通知我不够资格入学
and then regret to inform me I'm not good enough for your school?
现在我是很遗憾地通知你 我太够格
Well, I regret to inform you that I am good enough
还想知道为什么你不收我入学
and I want to know why you won't let me in here.
一听你的声音我就焦虑
Okay, uh, your voice is an anxiety trigger for me.
我要挪出去
I'm going to have to remove
坐到走廊那
myself from the situation and go sit in the hallway.
你能过来陪我吗 你看起来很冷静
Can you come with me? You have a very calming presence.
谢谢 几乎没人这么看我
Thank you. So few people think that about me.
但我要和Max一起
But I should stay with Max.
不 我能搞定 你把她带走吧
No, I got this handled. You can have her.
以后不准你随便把我给出去了
This is the last time you give me to someone.
Max 你的果馅饼非常出色 问题在于你的态度
Max, your tart was excellent. The problem was your attitude.
你没有表现出想要入学的热情
You showed no passion of wanting to be in this school.
所以你才没被录取
And that is why you didn't get in.
你好像根本不在乎
It seemed like you didn't want it.
不 不 不 我的态度是这样而已
No, no, no, that's just my attitude.
我装作我什么都不想要
I act like I don't want
是因为我从来没得到过我想要的东西
anything because I never got anything I wanted.
但是我从来都没有
But I do want to go to this
这么渴望要进入这学校
school more than I've ever wanted anything.
这是我的理想 是我的梦想
It's my fantasy and my dream,
你他喵别逼我说些恶心 玛丽苏的话的话好吗
and please stop making me use these horrible, horrible words!
就收我进来 好吗
Just let me in, okay?
好吧
Okay.
神马 真的么
Wait, for real?
没错 我想看看你的热情是不是跟你的手艺一样感动人
Yes. I needed to see if your passion was as good as your pastry
而你刚刚已经证明给我看了
and you just showed me it was.
很高兴你来到我们学校 大厨
I'm thrilled to have you on board, chef.
谢了 大厨
Thanks, chef.
Bebe恐慌症发作了 她要捉着她的柠檬
Bebe is having a panic attack and needs to hold her lemon.
有人见到过她的柠檬吗
Has anyone seen her lemon?
Caroline 他收了我了 我要去糕点学校了
Caroline, he let me in. I'm going to pastry school.
现在你们都得叫姐做"大厨"了
Everybody has to call me "Chef" Now!
你做到了 大厨
You did it, chef!
你要去小册子上介绍的糕点学校上学了
You're going to the pastry school from the brochure!
还不快感谢我翻了你的黄书
Aren't you glad I looked at your porn?
我们是室友 都是单身的 没想到吧
We're roommates. Both single. Quelle surprise.
那Max 你填好这些表格 你就是正式录取了
So Max, once you fill out these, you will be officially enrolled.
还有就是要交学费
And of course we will need your tuition check.
嗯哼 3000刀 对我们来说挺多的
Yup. $3,000. It's a lot for us.
不过我们会再省钱的 厕纸只用半层
But if we make some cutbacks, 1/2-ply toilet paper.
我特么在逗谁呢 厕纸 餐巾也不用了
Who am I kidding? No toilet paper, diner napkins.
慢着 学费是24000刀
No, tuition is 24,000.
不过小册子上写的是3000刀一年啊
But the brochure said $3,000 a year.
你看错了 是3000刀一门课
You misread it. It's $3,000 a unit.
一年有8门课 一共24000
There is eight units per year. 24,000.
要24000刀 我们可没那钱
It costs $24,000? We can't pay that.
噢 天啊 我这辈子都不可能来这上课
Oh, my God, now I'm never gonna be able to come here
老娘刚刚才认了我想来
and I just admitted I wanted to!
我说过我要什么的话我都收回来
I take back everything I ever said about wanting anything.
Max 你不能就这样一走了之
Max, you can't just storm out.
你的脸才不能一走了之
Your face can't just storm out!
听着 为了让她能来这上课我什么都愿意干
Look, I will do anything for that girl to go to this school.
我可以在这办公室打工 来帮忙付学费
In exchange for tuition, I could work in the office.
Bebe很明显要人来帮忙分担压力
Bebe clearly needs someone to help take the pressure off
又有谁比我这个心理正常
and who better than a mentally stable
的沃顿毕业生更合适呢
Wharton graduate like myself?
不过我什么都能做 帮你洗地板都行好吗
But I'll do anything. I'll even wash your floors, okay?
虽然我真的不是很想做这个
Although I'm sure there's something better than that.
不过你要我洗地板的话 我马上去洗
But if you need me to wash the floors, I will wash the floors.
虽然我更想做其他的事代替
Really would prefer to do anything else,
不过我还是会洗的 因为
but I'll do it, 'cause
为了让她能来这上课我在所不惜
I'll do anything to get her into this school.
求你别让我洗地板
Please no floors.
好吧 我跟我同事谈谈 然后再通知你吧
Okay, I will talk it over with my staff and I will let you know.
噢 不 不
Oh, no, no.
我知道这是怎么回
I've seen what happens
你说"再通知你吧"就没想着通知我
when you give people the "I'll let you know."
在你当面告诉我之前 我哪里都不会去
I'm not going anywhere until you let me know to my face.
用你这张帅气迷死人不偿命的脸
With your face. Your beautiful, beautiful face.
Max 我们还不够穷吗
Max, we're not poor enough?
你竟然还要在家里 像流浪汉一样用桶烧垃圾取暖
You're starting a hobo trash fire in our apartment?
没错 我在烧我的黄书跟糕点学校的小册子
Yup. I'm burning my porn and pastry school brochure.
就是 我所有的梦想
You know, all my fantasies.
生活教会了我一件事
If I learned anything in life
没有什么比我的梦想更不靠谱的了
it's that nothing's more flammable than my dreams.
那些是我的连袜便鞋吗
Are those my slipper socks in there?
嗯 那些也不能忍
Yeah, those needed to die too.
好吧 你在家里
Well, while you were in our
举办燃烧人节庆的时候
living room hosting a burning man festival,
我在糕点学校做好了勤工俭学的安排
I was at the pastry school getting us a work-study arrangement.
所以
And...
- 你要去糕点学校了  - 真的么
- You're going to pastry school. - No way!
拿好了 你的校服
Here you go. Your school uniform.
我的名字会印在这上面
This is where my name's gonna go!
我的厨师名 Conchita Bonfire
My chef name, Conchita Bonfire.
谢谢你
Thank you for this.
为我做的一切
And for everything.
你不用谢我
You don't have to thank me.
因为等我学成了
'Cause with your new
我会像金卡戴珊利用侃爷一样利用你
skills I'm gonna use you like Kim uses Kanye.
又或者侃爷利用卡戴珊 不知道他们谁占的便宜多点
Or Kanye uses Kim. I'm not sure which of them is winning.
你给我安排的这勤工俭学是怎样的
What kind of work-study arrangement did you make for me?
其实更像是给我们俩安排的
It's more of a work-study arrangement for us.
我会在办公室里帮Bebe忙
I'll be working in the office helping out Bebe,
所以我勤工 你俭学
so I'm working, you're studying.
你要在我学校里工作 (你像个)老妈
You're working at my school? Mom!
== 破产姐妹 第三季 第9集【H-SGDK】字幕组倾情奉献 ==
== 【H-SGDK】字幕组欢迎各位加入
有意者请加QQ群109164858，注明 字幕组+申请职位即可 ==
目前总资产：2.5刀
种族梗
另有梗 Calvin Klein曾在新加坡的监狱里举行过发布会
Max看来吸了点大麻
校对表示好痛……
James Franco在电影127小时饰演艾伦・洛斯顿 后者在现实中得截肢保命
音近Harmless (无害)
乖孩子们 校对才不会说Porn hub是免费黄片网
tests = 试验或考试的梗
用于筛查子宫颈癌 是种很简单的试验
tart 兼有贱女人和果馅饼的意思
Max这杀气冲天的样子
Han你在作死！
stop'n shop 连锁超市
Cheater当然可解作小三 Max两者肯定也有……
请自个儿参考先前说的梗
Max随口说的和法国沾边的词儿 来和法国大厨打招呼
Sephora丝芙兰 不用解释吧 小翻在那刚买了个洗脸刷~
种族梗
还是那句 双关在"把她吃了就跑"
燃烧人节庆 一年一度在美国内华达州黑石沙漠举办的活动
被许多参与者描述为社区 激进的自我表达 以及彻底自力更生的实验